The security fast C chart of SSC
Lambda Delay Time so that you guys
can see it, other quite hole Ted Talk friends, it will be
visible, I am taking it in this mix, you will
see how good it is,
it means it goes down, it comes up, it comes up, it is
suggested friends, we have to take an
express in it, that is why
friends, I am giving you stock
Edward, we will see, we should have the experience of all the things,
see guys,
I am trying to tell you that
if this stock shows a good rise in tomorrow's section,
almost our
level of 1460 means today's level, it
breaks in tomorrow's section, then
our first target will be directly
1490, our second target will be 1530, it is
not seen in tomorrow's interdiction, so
I feel that you have not carried forward the position, it will be
visible, why we have to carry forward the
guide, it is quite hole for the first reason
and the risk remote shock management
that we have to take is also according to this.  The
stoploss will remain simple, level
not
quick and now this level is approximately 1431,
our stoploss will be at this level,
why friends see, almost its previous one was placed
here, almost here and at the
level of 1435 10:30, Suraj, I want to
say that its support will be formed here
and I feel that the
level of 1435 is looking quite the best one in it,
so guys, now
I will put our Star Plus in this, this 1435 1430 level,
our first target on your side will be the
second of 2019 and the car drive,
this level of 1530, which is going to
give importance to the bottom side, we will not do it at all, actually we will not do it, the
top is
quite upside down, for this reason, otherwise, see
friends, I will tell you its job because I
love that we will see that if it is
in the stop section and we are not
able to call, then we do not have to do tailing in it,
take note of it directly friends because it will be
visible  Due to this stock being quite a heart attack, the
support line that we get in it is
not available daily, friends, due to this, friends,
I want to tell you that if
it opens widely in tomorrow's system or
breaks its level with good volume, then guys,
our two targets can be
seen in this,
we have to move ahead this week by just buying in the suicide number, we will
meet about ICICI Lombard in the next video, till then
Jai Hind Vande